{
    "subject": "resource/Suman_(actor)",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Suman was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8574703335762024,
            "question": "Is Suman's birthplace in Asia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7603491544723511,
            "question": "Where was Suman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.526272714138031,
            "question": "What country is Suman from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46272560954093933,
            "question": "Can you tell me a famous person born in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43846625089645386,
            "question": "Is there a historical landmark in Suman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31921273469924927,
            "question": "Could you describe the climate of Suman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2962768077850342,
            "question": "Are there any festivals celebrated in Suman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2761843800544739,
            "question": "Do you know any other details about Suman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06114732101559639,
            "question": "What are some popular cultures from India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.049140166491270065,
            "question": "What language is commonly spoken in India?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Suman was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8035_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular cultures from India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8035_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any other details about Suman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8035_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any festivals celebrated in Suman's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8035_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8035_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide different information about Suman's birthplace, including Madras of present-day Tamil Nadu (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8035/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8035/re-ranker-msmarco/84.txt), but not India in general. Therefore, the statement \"Suman was born in India\" is not supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention multiple individuals named Suman, and in all cases, they indicate that these Sumans were born in India. For example:\n\n- The document at `18.txt` states \"Suman was born in a Tulu-speaking family in Madras of present-day Tamil Nadu.\"\n- Another document at `45.txt` states \"Adhyayan Suman was born on January 13, 1988 in Bombay, Maharashtra, India.\" \n- And the document at `57.txt` or `88.txt` (they are identical) states \"Shekhar Suman was born on June 14, 1960 in Bombay, Maharashtra, India.\"\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context, the statement that Suman was born in India is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided about Suman being born in Ludhiana, India (point 1) conflicts with the birth locations mentioned in points 2 and 3, which state that Suman was born in a Tulu-speaking family in Madras of present-day Tamil Nadu.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}